{
    "subject": "resource/New_Wet_Kojak",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/isPrimaryTopicOf",
    "object": "http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_Wet_Kojak",
    "human_readable": "New Wet Kojak is the primary topic of New Wet Kojak.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9842537641525269,
            "question": "What is the primary topic of New Wet Kojak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8501800894737244,
            "question": "Can you describe the potential themes explored in New Wet Kojak based on its title?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8445321917533875,
            "question": "Is there a connection between the title and the content of New Wet Kojak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7852453589439392,
            "question": "What genre or category might New Wet Kojak fall under?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7373624444007874,
            "question": "What kind of imagery might the title 'New Wet Kojak' evoke?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7094865441322327,
            "question": "What kind of expectations might the title 'New Wet Kojak' set for an audience?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6640889048576355,
            "question": "How does the unusual title of New Wet Kojak likely attract viewers or readers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.360377699136734,
            "question": "What are some possible interpretations of the word 'Kojak' in this context?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15255729854106903,
            "question": "How does the use of words like 'New' and 'Wet' contribute to the overall meaning of the title?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.02584925852715969,
            "question": "Do you think the title is intended to be humorous, serious, or something else?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=New Wet Kojak is the primary topic of New Wet Kojak.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4649_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the use of words like 'New' and 'Wet' contribute to the overall meaning of the title?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4649_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some possible interpretations of the word 'Kojak' in this context?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4649_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the unusual title of New Wet Kojak likely attract viewers or readers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4649_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4649_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4649_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4649_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4649_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4649_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4649_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4649_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4649_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4649_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4649_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* The band \"New Wet Kojak\" is indeed the primary topic of all the provided documents. Each document talks about the band's history, music, and performances.\n\nTherefore, the answer to your question is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide detailed information about New Wet Kojak, including its members (Scott McCloud, Johnny Temple, Geoff Turner, Charles Bennington, Nick Pelliciotto), their history as a side project to Girls Against Boys, and details of their music. Therefore, it is accurate to say that New Wet Kojak is the primary topic of the documents provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}